Alyssa S. Cucunato

acucunato18@gmail.com • linkedin • github • portfolio • Philadelphia, Pennsylvania • 856-287-3779

– Skilled Manager, Web Developer *–*

Dedicated and skilled manager with over a decade of progressive experience training and mentoring staff to deliver exceptional service while promoting organizational objectives and increasing revenue. Manage complex relationships, complete human resources tasks, and increase sales. Talented communicator able to calmly and effectively resolve conflict and address concerns. Analyze information and implement process improvements to achieve established goals.

- Store Operations
- Customer Service
- Inventory Management
- Relationship Development
- Project Management
- Staff Training & Leadership
- System & Process Improvement
- Visual Merchandising
- Conflict Resolution

Career Experience

Senior Store Operations Specialist, Henri Bendel, New York, NY

2018 to 2019

Supported smooth store operations by managing all store communications, sending weekly emails, updating the communication portal, executing transfers, and maintaining knowledge of products, incentives, and store programs. Partnered with merchants, finance, PR, marketing, and visual merchandising to coordinate distribution of weekly information, including product updates, visual guides, signage, and reports. Trained and mentored store managers to accurately and efficiently complete operations processes, and perform inventory control, cycle counts, and store transfers. Provided leadership, training, and support to employees to encourage collaboration, teamwork, and personal growth. Assisted with resolution of customer issues by researching incidents and ensuring resolutions that meet store standards.

- Designed and distributed new management on-boarding training guide that resulted in consistent and seamless onboarding of new management staff, and reduced training time by half.
- Established and launched Bendel Experience Program across 28 stores, improving customer in-store experience 35%.
- Coordinated annual store manager conference in partnership with operations manager, developing programs, marketing, and visual plans that drove business results.

Store Manager, Henri Bendel, Cherry Hill, NJ | King of Prussia, PA | Santa Clara, CA

2014 to 2018

Assisted in managing retail store, and oversaw sales and operations while providing excellent leadership and guidance to staff members. Performed opening and closing procedures, monitored and maintained store inventory, and applied promotions to improve sales. Recruited, hired, trained, mentored, and disciplined employees to promote professional development and maintain excellent customer service. Maintained sales records, designed employee schedules, and addressed customer service issues.

• Increased store sales in Santa Clara 15% by analyzing key business metrics, identifying opportunities, and implementing impactful solutions, including adjusting store goals and objectives.

...continued...

Alyssa S. Cucunato

Page 2

- Launched store social media program at King of Prussia store, managing monthly Instagram calendar, partnering with marketing and public relations team to promote in-store events and curate content.
- Trained and on-boarded new store managers company-wide, and acted as area manager, completing
 weekly store visits to complete visual walk-throughs and provide constructive feedback.
- Recruited and mentored #1 seller in district and store, delivering 35% of total store volume.

Co-Manager, Henri Bendel, Cherry Hill, NJ

2011 to 2014

Managed store operations for luxury department store and oversaw sales while providing excellent leadership and guidance to staff members. Partnered with store manager to develop goals, manage merchandising and visual displays, and support, train, and mentor sales team. Monitored and maintained store inventory, and clearly communicated promotions and events to customers and staff to improve sales. Recruited, hired, trained, mentored, and disciplined employees to promote professional development and maintain excellent customer service. Maintained sales records, designed employee schedules, and addressed customer service issues.

- Surpassed sales plan by 10% in first year, and by 15% over prior year in 2013.
- Recruited and trained #1 seller in store, ranked top 20 companywide, who was responsible for 30% of store sales volume.

Full-Time Sales Associate, Juicy Couture, King of Prussia, PA

2008 to 2011

Provided sales support for a designer brand store. Delivered exceptional service and addressed customer needs by utilizing client relationships and strategic selling skills to maximize sales. Collaborated with colleagues to deliver high-level service and create positive working environment. Followed company guidelines to complete and maintain visual merchandising displays, and trained and mentored new sales staff.

Education

UPenn LPS Coding Bootcamp

University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA

Bachelor of Science in Fashion Merchandising

Philadelphia University, Philadelphia, PA

Study Abroad, American University of Rome, Fashion Merchandising